<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Seung Hyun (Sam) Min</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Seung Hyun (Sam) Min</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Favorite clarinet clips</title>
      <link>/blog/clarinet_clips/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/clarinet_clips/</guid>
      <description>Here are some of my favorite clarinet clips. I have watched them countless times.
Tchaikovsky’s Nutcracker for the clarinet and orchestraSergey’s playing is so lyrical. He sings with the clarinet. I can listen to his playing all day.
Rossini’s Introduction, Theme and VariationsValentin’s articulation is god-level. His conducting is also god-level. Everything about this so god. His cadenza in the end is legendary!
Spohr #2 concertoThe soloist effortlessly plays this notoriously difficult piece.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>During high school, I was diagnosed with a nerve injury on my right hand from playing the clarinet, leaving me with no choice but to become ambidextrous. I had to longitudinally retrain my brain so that my left hand could properly write alphabets and hold chopsticks, the responsibilities that had been formerly assigned to my right hand. The experiences from my recovery sparked my interest in neural plasticity. For my undergraduate education, I pursued Anatomy and Cell Biology at McGill University and graduated within the top 10% of my class on June 2017.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>/pubs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/pubs/</guid>
      <description>Note: Preprints are not peer-reviewed. Co-first authorships are denoted with *.
  Seung Hyun Min*, Shijia Chen*, Jinling Xu, Bingzhen Chen, Hui Chen, Yuwen Wang, Jiawei Zhou, Xudong Yu. A comparison of therapies using Eyetronix Flicker Glass and standard adhesive patches in children with anisometropic amblyopia: A randomized controlled trial (Preprint). medRxiv. *co-first authors pdf
  Seung Hyun Min, Ling Gong, Alex S. Baldwin, Alexandre Reynaud, Zhifen He, Jiawei Zhou, Robert F.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breathe by Lee hi</title>
      <link>/blog/breathe_leehi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/breathe_leehi/</guid>
      <description>Breathe is one of my favorite songs. Many covers have been recorded. Here are my favorites.
Original by Lee hiThis is the original recording of the song.
Han Dong GeunHan’s control of dynamic is amazing. His arrangement strays from the original but is absolutely beautiful.
Kyu HyunHis voice is beautiful. Very clear and resonant. This rendition is very faithful to the original</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>