<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Seung Hyun (Sam) Min</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Seung Hyun (Sam) Min</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>During high school, I was diagnosed with a nerve injury on my right hand from playing the clarinet, leaving me with no choice but to become ambidextrous. I had to longitudinally retrain my brain so that my left hand could properly write alphabets and hold chopsticks, the responsibilities that had been formerly assigned to my right hand. The experiences from my recovery sparked my interest in neural plasticity. For my undergraduate education, I pursued Anatomy and Cell Biology at McGill University and graduated within the top 10% of my class on June 2017.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>/pubs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/pubs/</guid>
      <description>Yidong Wu, Meiping Xu, Junxiao Zhang, Jinjing Zhou, Minghui Wan, Zhiyue Dai, Tingting Peng, Seung Hyun Min, Fang Hou, Jiawei Zhou and Xinping Yu (2020). Can clinical measures of postoperative binocular function predict the long-term stability of postoperative alignment in intermittent exotropia? Journal of Ophthalmology.vol. 2020, 7392165. pdf
  Ling Gong*, Seung Hyun Min*, Shijia Chen, Junhan Wei, Deying Kong, Chunwen Tao, Peng Zhang, Pi-Chun Huang, Jiawei Zhou (2020).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breathe by Lee hi</title>
      <link>/blog/breathe_leehi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/breathe_leehi/</guid>
      <description>Breathe is one of my favorite songs. Many covers have been recorded. Here are my favorites.
Original by Lee hiThis is the original recording of the song.
Han Dong GeunHan’s control of dynamic is amazing. His arrangement strays from the original but is absolutely beautiful.
Kyu HyunHis voice is beautiful. Very clear and resonant. This rendition is very faithful to the original</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Flight of the Bumblebee is a must-learn piece</title>
      <link>/blog/bumblebee/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/bumblebee/</guid>
      <description>R MarkdownThis is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
When you click the Knit button a document will be generated that includes both content as well as the output of any embedded R code chunks within the document. You can embed an R code chunk like this:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>