<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Seung Hyun (Sam) Min</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Seung Hyun (Sam) Min</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Why Flight of the Bumblebee is a great etude</title>
      <link>/blog/bumblebee/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/bumblebee/</guid>
      <description>I play the clarinet as a hobby although I used to play it competitively during high school. Unfortunately, since I began my undergraduate studies, I have stopped receiving lessons, which are quite expensive. So during undergrad, my playing ability rarely improved. However, perhaps thanks to COVID-19, I have had more spare time recently and have been able to find practice routines that have worked for me to become a better player.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exercise Solutions for Data Analysis for the Life Sciences in R</title>
      <link>/blog/da4ls_ans/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/da4ls_ans/</guid>
      <description>I have made an answer key for a statistics book entitled: Data Analysis for the Life Sciences in R. Here is the link. Happy coding!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exercise Solutions for Data Analysis for the Life Sciences with R</title>
      <link>/blog/rstats/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/rstats/</guid>
      <description>I have made an answer key for a statistics book entitled: Data Analysis for the Life Sciences in R. Here is the link. Happy coding!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Favorite clarinet clips</title>
      <link>/blog/clarinet_clips/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/clarinet_clips/</guid>
      <description>Here are some of my favorite clarinet clips. I have watched them countless times.
Tchaikovsky’s Nutcracker for the clarinet and orchestraSergey’s playing is so lyrical. He sings with the clarinet. I can listen to his playing all day.
Rossini’s Introduction, Theme and VariationsValentin’s articulation is god-level. His conducting is also god-level. Everything about this so god. His cadenza in the end is legendary!
Spohr #2 concertoThe soloist effortlessly plays this notoriously difficult piece.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>During high school, I was diagnosed with a nerve injury within my right hand from playing the clarinet, leaving me with no choice but to become ambidextrous. I had to longitudinally retrain my brain so that my left hand could properly write alphabets and hold chopsticks, the responsibilities that had been formerly assigned to my right hand. The experiences from my recovery sparked my interest in neural plasticity. For my undergraduate education, I pursued Anatomy and Cell Biology at McGill University and graduated within the top 10% of my class on June 2017.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>/pubs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/pubs/</guid>
      <description>Note: Preprints are not peer-reviewed. Co-first authorships are denoted with *.
  Seung Hyun Min, Ling Gong, Alex S. Baldwin, Alexandre Reynaud, Zhifen He, Jiawei Zhou, Robert F. Hess. Ocular dominance plasticity: measurement reliability and variability (Preprint). bioRxiv. pdf
  Seung Hyun Min*, Shijia Chen*, Jinling Xu, Bingzhen Chen,Hui Chen, Yuwen Wang, Jiawei Zhou, Xudong Yu. A Randomized Clinical Trial Comparing Eyetronix Flicker Glass and Patching for Treatment of Amblyopia in Children Reveals Similar Improvements in Vision (2021).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breathe by Lee hi</title>
      <link>/blog/breathe_leehi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/breathe_leehi/</guid>
      <description>Breathe is one of my favorite songs. Many covers have been recorded. Here are my favorites.
Original by Lee hiThis is the original recording of the song.
Han Dong GeunHan’s control of dynamic is amazing. His arrangement strays from the original but is absolutely beautiful.
Kyu HyunHis voice is beautiful. Very clear and resonant. This rendition is very faithful to the original</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
