<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>about on Seung Hyun (Sam) Min</title>
    <link>/tags/about/</link>
    <description>Recent content in about on Seung Hyun (Sam) Min</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>During high school, I was diagnosed with a nerve injury on my right hand from playing the clarinet, leaving me with no choice but to become ambidextrous. I had to longitudinally retrain my brain so that my left hand could properly write alphabets and hold chopsticks, the responsibilities that had been formerly assigned to my right hand. The experiences from my recovery sparked my interest in neural plasticity. For my undergraduate education, I pursued Anatomy and Cell Biology at McGill University and graduated within the top 10% of my class on June 2017.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>/pubs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/pubs/</guid>
      <description>Note: Preprints are not peer-reviewed. Co-first authors are labelled with asterisks(*).
  Seung Hyun Min*, Shijia Chen*, Jinling Xu, Bingzhen Chen, Hui Chen, Yuwen Wang, Jiawei Zhou, Xudong Yu. A comparison of therapies using Eyetronix Flicker Glass and standard adhesive patches in children with anisometropic amblyopia: A randomized controlled trial (Preprint). medRxiv. *co-first authors pdf
  Seung Hyun Min, Ling Gong, Alex S. Baldwin, Alexandre Reynaud, Zhifen He, Jiawei Zhou, Robert F.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>